Jack Hardy

Flat 107, Piccadilly Residence, Piccadilly Court, York, YO1 9SZ 07932 696325, jackjohnhardy@outlook.com, https://www.jackjohnhardy.com

As an enthusiastic and dedicated computer science student at The University of York, I am looking forward to the challenge of an industrial placement. My work experience in hospitality and particularly in dealing with customers, has allowed me to develop key skills such as communication, teamwork, and working under pressure. I am really looking forward to implementing these skills in an industry environment.

Education

2021 - Present

BSc Computer Science (with a Year in Industry) - The University of York

Second Year Modules: (Average: 69%)

- Intelligent Systems 1: Search & Representation (74%)
- Systems & Devices 2: System Software & Security (50%)
- Theory 3: Computability & Complexity (69%)
- Data 2: Data Analysis & Management (69%)
- Human-Computer Interaction 2: User Experience (65%)
- Engineering 1: Introduction to Software & Systems Engineering
- Systems & Devices 3: Advanced Computer Systems
- Intelligent Systems 2: Machine Learning & Optimisation
- Software 3: Functional Programming with Applications

First Year Modules: (Average: 71%)

- Software 1: Foundations of Programming for Computer Science (94%)
- Software 2: Object Oriented Data Structures & Algorithms (78%)
- Systems & Devices 1: Introduction to Computing Systems (40%)
- Theory 1: Mathematical Foundations of Computer Science (74%)
- Theory 2: Formal Languages & Automata (71%)
- Human-Computer Interaction 1: Introduction to User Centred Design (67%)
- Data 1: Introduction to Data Science (56%)

2019 - 2021 Dyffryn Conwy High School (Sixth form)

A-Level: Mathematics (A), Physics (A), Welsh Baccalaureate (A)

BTEC: Engineering (Distinction*)

2014 - 2019 **Dyffryn Conwy High School**

GCSEs: 4x A*, 3x A, 2x B, 1x C including:

Maths (A*), Computer Science (A)

Work Experience and Volunteering

2016 - Present

Elen's Castle Hotel & Restaurant, Snowdonia National Park

My responsibilities in my family's business are numerous and wide-ranging and I have frequently had to take sole responsibility in the absence of my parents due to ill health.

In my role I have developed valuable interpersonal skills from taking care of numerous customers on a daily basis, as a result I am personable, approachable, adaptable, and friendly. I am able to prioritise, delegate and work in a close knit, responsive and dynamic team.

2019 - 2020 Volunteer Maths Tutor

Classroom and individual tutoring to struggling year 7 students.

Technical Skills and Projects

Python (self-taught)

JavaC

Assembly Language Programing

• Git

• Balsamiq Wireframes

· Visual Studio Code

• InteliJ IDEA

• Notepad++

• Xilinx ISE Design Suite

TerminusRP Sep 2022 - Present (Hobby Project)

A DayZ Server that reworks most of the game to provide a unique community and experience to players.

This is a large project that encompasses many subprojects including:

- Creating, and coding DayZ mods.

- Artworks (in-game textures, logos, maps, etc.)

- Creating and coding a Discord Bot.

- Creating a website.

- Hosting and managing a game server.

JackJohnHardy.com Dec 2022 - Present

My personal website that includes more information

about me, including a portfolio.

Piazza Panic (Project Lead) Oct 2022 - Present

A kitchen simulator game for presentation at open

days for the University of York.

This game will be designed to the specification of our client from the university, and will be implemented from in Java using the LibGDX library.

This project is a part of the Engineering 1 module.

BirdGame (Individual

Research Project)

Sep 2020 - Jun 2021

A simple but enjoyable mobile game as a part of the Individual Research Project for Welsh Baccalaureate A

Level.

This game was created using Unity and C#.

Whitehaven Minecraft Server (Owner) Jan 2020 - Jan 2022

A Vanilla+ Minecraft Server and Community. In my time running this server it received over £250 in player donations which more than covered the server expenses. I have since archived the server and moved on from playing Minecraft along with many of the players who played the Whitehaven server.

Achievements, Interests, and Hobbies

I received a Gold Crest Award for Engineering Education Scheme for Wales for completing a project with Airbus, Broughton in 2020. I was awarded the Conwy Valley Rotary Prize for Exceptional Performance in my GCSEs. Following that I was invited to join the Seren Network during my time in 6th form, which involved participating in master classes and attending the national conference. I spend a lot of my spare time gaming, and I enjoy trips to the cinema. I have travelled internationally and particularly enjoy skiing.

For more information about me and my projects, visit: https://jackjohnhardy.com

References available upon request.